Thanks for comin', everyone!
Did you all have fun?
What's going on…?
B-Beats me…
You really are an interesting guy, Ume!
Alright, that's it for today!
Everybody head home!
Hey, are there any places
to get take-out around here?
Why…?
What do you mean, "why"?
We're having an after-party!
Woo! Cheers! That's a wrap!
What…
Why are we doin' this outside?
You can't do a banquet indoors!
- The hell is going on here?
- Scoot in or you'll get wet, Sakura.
That was quite the rainstorm.
Man, everything looks great.
I wouldn't expect any less
of a bar district's menu!
Alright, down the hatch!
Delicious!
These are all delish!
- It really is good.
- This is great, too!
Ah, they did give us some lemon!
Squeeze it on your own food, dumbass!
I-I'm surprised they have
appetites in a situation like this.
Right?
You agree, Suo? Thank goodness,
I thought I was alone in that.
Oh, no, I'm just on a diet.
A diet?!
What's his deal?
How can he eat with a guy
he was only just fighting?
I mean…
Can you even call that a fight?
How could he forgive that?
I know I couldn't…
Oh? Something wrong, Togame?
You haven't touched a thing.
I'm sorry.
If you look at the lead-up
to this fight… It was all my fault.
Lion's Head going rotten,
yesterday's confrontation, today,
all of it.
I'm really sorry.
Kame, I'm at fault, too!
You heard 'em.
Whatcha wanna do, Sakura?
The choice is yours.
Huh?!
I'll take any punishment you give.
That's the right thing to do.
Promise me!
You'll become a cool guy!
And you'll never be lame again!
You hear me?!
I promise.
Alright, that's the end of that!
Oh? What's this?
Mmm!
It's fried burdock!
Ume. You're top dog, so why do you
seem to have so much fun?
Well, you see, I love to eat.
I love eating, too! Curry's my favorite!
What about you?
I'm a rice omelette man.
Oh, but I'm not so into the food itself.
What I'm about is having
a good time eating with everyone.
Chatting about stuff,
laughing my head off.
It makes all the bad stuff stop mattering.
Nothing's more fun than times like this.
That's why I'm having tons of fun right now!
And hey, all that?
It has nothing at all to do with me being top dog.
Yeah, that's right…
I remembered how much fun I had
before I took over.
When everyone laughed, it made me happy, too.
But I didn't realize it then.
I ended up thinking I'd
have fun if I became top dog.
Why didn't I notice, though…?
I mean, people don't go, "Man, I love oxygen!"
with each breath, do they?
You didn't notice because you were
already having enough fun it didn't register.
Good thing you noticed before you lost it all.
Really. I'm happy for you.
Hey, can I ask one more thing?
Hm?
If you knew all that already,
why did you become top dog?
Because I wanted to have fun
eating with everyone all the time!
If everyone's happy and smiling,
then I can enjoy my food.
That's why, when I thought of
what I could do in this town,
I settled on being Furin's top dog. That's all.
Being top dog wasn't my goal,
but rather the things it would let me do.
If there was a better way,
I'd probably have done that instead.
But if that happened,
I wouldn't be here eating with you guys!
You really are something else, Ume.
You actually understood yourself
before becoming top dog.
Not quite. I didn't "become" top dog.
I was made top dog.
You can't take the spot on your own.
I was able to become top dog
because everyone supported me.
They agreed with what I wanted to do,
and helped make it reality.
That made me realize something
when I became top dog.
My wishes weren't mine alone.
And because I want to grant those wishes,
no matter how hard, unfair,
or unreasonable things get,
I'll never lose.
You're carrying everything on your back, Ume.
Your punches are light.
Do you know why that is?
Because there's nothing behind them.
Choji…
Aw, man.
My punches really were light!
I can't beat that!
Later! Come hang with us sometime!
The food here was tasty and all,
but we've got tons of good stuff, too!
Can we?!
You bet!
I wish I brought something for you…
Ah!
I forgot I bought a red bean bun at Saboten!
Want it? Their bread's great, even cold!
Man, that's way beyond just "cold" by now.
Thanks!
Come get a fresh one sometime!
Mhm.
See ya later!
See ya!
And they're gone.
Mm.
Hey, Kame.
Hm?
I get it.
I know an apology won't fix what I did.
Mm.
But I don't know what
I should do to make it right.
I don't even know what I can do.
But I still…
I…
I need you guys.
So please…
Same here.
I can't take back what I did.
I want to make amends somehow,
but I don't know what to do other than apologize.
But that's all the more reason…
I have to face them.
How about we try to find
an answer together this time?
Mhm!
What's so funny?
It may be all smooshed,
but it's still a good bean bun!
It's real good!
I wonder how good a fresh one is?
Huh? Is it raining again?
You're right! That sure is weird.
Even though the sun is out…
Welcome back.
Sasaki! Don't tell me
you were waiting the whole time!
U-Um!
I told you to leave it to us.
It's done.
Thank you…
Thank you all so much!
We're baaack!
Welcome ba… wait,
you've already been patched up?
- Kotoha! Your bro's back home!
- So what went down with Lion's Head?
We're, uh, friends now?
- You always come back a mess.
- Well, we got home safe.
You okay?
This is nothin'.
You look surprisingly clean.
I'm not really the sweating type.
You're a mess, too, Sakura.
Welcome back.
Because you're alone.
I was able to become top dog
because everyone supported me.
They agreed with what I wanted to do,
and helped make it reality.
What's up, Sakura?
You've been clammed up the whole way back.
I'm leaving.
Eh?! What's wrong, Sakura?
Wait just a sec.
What're you…?!
This is a day to remember! We gotta celebrate!
Kotoha! Get us special coffees!
There's nothing to celebrate here!
You had a nice conversation with your fight.
That makes this Conversation Day!
Huh?! What kinda nonsense is that?!
What's Conversation Day?
Hmm, maybe something like Salad Day?
- Celebrate on your own.
- Hey.
I wanna talk. With you.
I thought I could become top dog on my own.
That the strongest guy would be top dog.
But it looks like I was wrong…
So, how was it?
Your conversation with Togame?
I mean, it wasn't, really.
I didn't hear anything from his fists.
I get it now! That's how you took it, huh?
How surprising! Sakura's a romanticist!
Sakura, that's silly even for you.
What's your problem?! Stop laughing!
Man, I'm sorry.
Guess I didn't explain well enough.
But you really are a straightforward guy, huh?
This ain't telepathy.
Even I don't hear anything from fists!
When I said punches are a language,
I didn't mean actual words.
I meant they're a way to make
thoughts known. To understand.
A method older than language. More primitive.
So what they can convey is also primitive.
Primitive how?
Y'know, things like love and hate.
My eyes!
Hang on, Sugishita!
Look at that poison spray!
What are you guys doing?!
You're cleaning that yourselves!
Sorry, Kotoha.
So, while you were conversing with Togame,
you came to like the guy, yeah?
Huh?!
That's why you tried to punch Tomiyama afterward.
I think that's a sure sign
you had a real conversation.
S-So what if I did?!
Why is that something to celebrate?!
Well, that's obvious.
'Cause I'm happy for you!
Huh?
You see, I heard somebody
was coming from out of town.
I thought, "Now there's one unique guy.
Wonder what he's like?"
And after watching you yesterday
and today, I made up my mind.
You're a good guy.
And when a guy like you to comes to this town…
Of course it makes me happy.
Then we coulda just had a welcoming party.
That's better than Conversation Day.
Oh, hey, you're right!
That makes sense!
How.
Oh?
How do you accept people so easily?!
Pull them in?!
You got everyone in town,
even the guys at Furin…
I came to be top dog! To take you down!
But I can't do that…
I've never accepted anyone before…
That's why I aimed to get strong all on my own.
Hell, I came here so I could
become top dog and accept myself!
But… it turns out you need
other people's help to become top dog…
And since I can't accept people,
I can't be top dog…
W-Wait a sec, Sakura!
S-Sakura, you told me yesterday
that I wasn't lame!
But, well…
You're not lame.
You actually paid attention to me!
That made me super happy!
And that means you…!
Um…
Huh?! What was I trying to say, again?
Don't worry. He got the message.
So, Sakura,
do you know what it takes
to converse with your fists?
No, what?
You need to face each other,
and want to know the other guy.
And you did that.
That's how you conversed with Togame.
I wanna know.
What's his deal?
I'm not saying you gotta accept
everyone and everything,
but, well, if you want to accept people,
you have to face them first.
And you can do that.
And far as I can see,
you want to accept people.
You haven't given up on people.
And you don't have to.
Turn towards me.
- Do that, and you can be whatever you want.
- You'll be able to become what you wanted.
You can even become top dog!
'Kay?
I-If I become top dog,
that'd mean I beat you!
There is that! But that's
for future me to deal with!
Oh?
What's up, Sugishita? Gotta take a leak?
You're dead!
What, you wanna go?! Then let's go!
H-Hang on, Sugishita!
He had murder in his eyes this whole time!
What do you guys think you're doing?!
If you're gonna fight, take it outside!
[#10: Conversation]
Umemiya's got a soft spot for Kotoha, right?
He sure does.
Then that means Bofurin's real top dog is…
So you went and figured it out…